[{"topicId":"15","id":"15000","langCode":"en","question":"i+gvOjmq9Tva07NcXTj1D/39Cm3cUSZfqSAL+pIq9PBf/W3kwMOuwkuolXeEKpQFgwFEhOvfa9GlLv7NlMhw5iNi1xkA7sJXXPGR/XncboQ\u003d","answers":["when","what","which","why"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17wUJ7GYJ1O0hxv6qd0UvJBqFS8DAFItkcnC6ULufufzIvAtHdJzAEYGQYlavozN2Tig08miPXTiHHLuLUciH+IT5IHGzJZV2xnt9m3RUa5xt4qeJ7JYG9FHJZ2ohEa4XLH/4eYMECuMOVhKZUjchxwh7ZJYOgQ0+aZZZg7A0PDTZHCl5JxTQPwxICxj9AMUF68yMsggedNbj6E04/mVzBWfClZ4bCOtk+ylir3oV9B1M3V7bPeoweB91ox8hfoZTRlA0vGKF9TiR7uzqKxro7o\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15001","langCode":"en","question":"SzxhW7OhPLDaN/lHbVBCKKY7O2tq3UPGHoAaacboE0Le59lL2Y3j9JhLT7rCjJbLds+XX1XzG2lLsOTperAI8lsOvHILXiAaNpjwmy0Q9Ub+6m+A7svcrCld1KaD4x0ukExO0HCobOEinqRb1C42DbVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d","answers":["when","where","what","who"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17wUJ7GYJ1O0hxv6qd0UvJCkNKZuC6cwglx4k5z50W7U9dZxSDk53Ds62Rv/dLwtIIITLSebVlX74gZOgTOHUkkQTxO/wCVvhOtxL+g4Y9LHbOXEQf6AsauRZSFt7imAXbV/XCXlpkwf6acFuBOIbjZY+WSaB0ePZCTu6E3Wj1EEiM0CD/eTj7rfUTfNG26ST2gxvo5aLM+0tu1NSI9PsKlRBpGj4G9x5IcZPdcYm0D6G7cqraYPvvFAmj9Uk6Ya+K2etbl3fmpQeZphtuqP9BLpIhLmXyjjdy7ueYNEE35A4Gh2ifAyqgD2e7rcE4jy4A\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15002","langCode":"en","question":"YsqiALW5A/6EQfeGfObvoPNLwPIdxAdrRckVMAxjZ2EePyvOz9u2esbRhEF6eHDS25m3h89PL5vwS4leA6nBwrlwH8xRyG7Lky3dy/4bNPs\u003d","answers":["why","what","who","which"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17wUJ7GYJ1O0hxv6qd0UvJAk56+Zp5zd9YYyNVWTnV1ayZk2O4b5aHSrev+JDt6z28ZMZzwLQLw/kl/Tt9Vni/VwmTWc871BG/h2t9gjm8iKvZziMjf2ieo7vzo5Gi4mlRE0BVTJbXQokj+Au4tXnuFjXqIfOijxU5ALICw6XMzHp80DMSoW9mQIOTjKeQXO4XqB8oy09N47QYxtBEZej5YRNAVUyW10KJI/gLuLV57hU/rleebeteZld0FeETnIaHucRbbddTc7BMGK4vn3/hz5YuhTNFktmJqIEf0UUADg"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15003","langCode":"en","question":"P1MveXYtpjfImhTXdljJwjlUvKl5DlfaOKAsal6qv9aWF9u6SHX3K0QKoA7WA+alEiEzSY9DtMWzwZDMSkw1bw\u003d\u003d","answers":["how","when","whose","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ6luxVFZbIYARiAppvzdj4gtX9cJeWmTB/ppwW4E4huNjZTR7wq87UBQ7jl42qJUgilq05xaTeZw8re/6T9qmHxrzIyyCB501uPoTTj+ZXMFXWJHDeyjPwB9wE7KrLFViL11nFIOTncOzrZG/90vC0gl2Icc94iq7A98jir8XH9FEWFDj3REPdCBDK2AN7k5ux+747sEHvDHtrsSu5lctKTbn6WKTLcxi6JE7QNfyZa6Yy0yMChlYqyAujP0ilDRPu6GOL/G9hejEviMcLyiAmw"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15004","langCode":"en","question":"7550c9BmMI0Fv+lXzQvADOYs+pyF5/At4QSaw3bD9LfE6nOGE0Ejl9dL3lYe8AOHAEnqFbtShfUPZHQO7rVozA\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","when","which","whose"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ759dGi2qOUgUG5iCwqPDh+husiP946pvYVFzXl46ibceKuj6sf6eSC+A726mCyzBL2bzGmWyLv/9p+tBQsXLAuHCrZZW9Drp6HRN88yQbw7e1KfDCPTzvAgRjITNdjh2O6Z3s4z112h53grmGpqYRlxblIzabjfh6uju2bSueDorV/XCXlpkwf6acFuBOIbjZClKmPtzVJBDkhNmf5uQxBltgb7ccWSaKRxr7ysGDBg1sq7Wz5WLOy+Kkravexrt+1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15005","langCode":"en","question":"HAdNZX9UegOrX1Z4VD+9xLlJPhR5RdpkeT06ivmWXiVUjhoU114o4OXEE2UXlUZh","answers":["which","how","when","why"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xHeVrZK7KMY2f0hVhY3iQ4va+co2Db9hfkd+5+sa+asJmHXCqZHjRMbAHxim96t/t5fCVtL2UksNC/aIkIQxtK159NQgK3ddZF5ErJWoDOK0KGEkhsrvYdgKn2MuWTB22ojBiHmomaFZnukXuvPnOXe+x7b2AQ3TWAId2SKE6AD2EF0/LJbUcZc1bTxbM/B0tJDzfbr+UuUiCBLSttgLyfZ8AIQSXpLNolPtjeqaSVLgbP66yiEo350aefNXSKyeztyiQjOILvvA2uWf4LSylrPMyA34FJJMsWpdck3yTCVSdlCtsS5MDh1FEKGDhCPabH/4eYMECuMOVhKZUjchxwh7ZJYOgQ0+aZZZg7A0PDTAgwVko2enOQaYqR/LHiJLxgjKEf9c0nkykZX1tb8YVxaCR5B3SUMl43BEDPmS+y51DFs3swAEjjw20tiSklvdvHrU7h6/lYrdwqBPbxSUu51ypLz3qc+xPaVKkP6o5KpQaVrbaBPltPzURuvFqvJkw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15006","langCode":"en","question":"P1MveXYtpjfImhTXdljJwmf77bWEOEsj/7ktqADGVEPAHfVLgFVHHL8HEWuM2bZkoYdpuVFOHq5dxEEyPNm8EVsMAuj/ttpDDBz6M4/XoVg\u003d","answers":["when","whose","how","where"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/ro17YGleOom0zXgXJyz6HXd8dBFZSrKEzwYI3OZxZu9YLnQFsvlEUUs66eYnGhgWSsYydPzhFwyimXEw51DKz/0jhdYmUns1/scLDBhhxuSjvQUhP3j9L8qc78BsXPERtYhw8nM1QlKRT2betKJp18O8DHM9o8w7wgtkUjQ1kT0PNfeOmCfzFlHtafuA7iuJUbtyqtpg++8UCaP1STphr4aA25uq+8TiYPzcRgdbB9aAz7QNkVWY6F5xcEA04vnT4ALbE68Sv4M5qsclNkmBZi"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15007","langCode":"en","question":"yIJPJGA2z7ei0CKL5+wUTXMzKyrYKiykyYP/Uclg2wnxlpRZB7W1BXhl0ygBuFcD","answers":["wherever","which","what","who"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17rT9q4GvP8qOFwmGudjbV2mCYmSCrtU9MFeZicL1D1sVyGFtdrmEzipmI/kagEYFnk8qYs8QHSi3CemZPsuI4zNlcPnXLGZ3mWIdozMGD+FjsSJv8nZgZim3DIYdSt8/Wgxvo5aLM+0tu1NSI9PsKmVnCwRr2GmJxgoR5yzm002RF7+oaLTGVvAFxv1scLDabIOcjAwOxfl2B8g16GIHlIea4GGeoCgN6qCSZhmIHmRMeboECaul9uEhqpy1m748ahKEF6P3jTozWztg5dMISA4Qdcv3CwXwwTJymrho9EUuiGjsMbo5nOckE+JuM5WFYRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15008","langCode":"en","question":"RwSfMXx+rGZsQ8H9ah/Z+NKeZK8lvuAolTs1DU5AcAcL+q2hYi8YVBkkc4MNvaN3ZFtln/2AKYDowGa0UGrmeA\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","when","where","why"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/r35Fg4ojnt9kNDK5dHrcG+LMLJmPmJ7uav3Z0QuyQ4hEIcMCrWS3HiTxQQynb7cjD49hVtwodIqvpdR/LdLsS6rMVfZqYdRLpcZC+rxTGPf68yMsggedNbj6E04/mVzBVZPkD0zdnhkh9nWA/SWy78tX9cJeWmTB/ppwW4E4huNlj5ZJoHR49kJO7oTdaPUQQu627cur7FT2zBn3LKbrtZ49MkoIBfD8cxdXb9xqTxNOBodonwMqoA9nu63BOI8uA\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15009","langCode":"en","question":"Vfbf2K2ixv6/35KFAgwkPUTHcYEqSpzqkN3crfIICn5y9zfBwdiYcoK94tarBhnJ4nd/GheeDyVqyyWfLJcfVs2B3dtyqIGup9K6ZcQcHDJrqIi1ZgoyUnZHKat+CXozhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","whose","where","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/opALFR9mLayr4m9belYP2+q+u0qvq5e7zZuNmC1F6af6J51nIPtW+2x3AyvjqXBkhPTxxD/OTqTqVBV4MItY1kG/Z2nN3KQYKdzgG3NWfACPXWcUg5Odw7Otkb/3S8LSCXYhxz3iKrsD3yOKvxcf0U1RJTSc7gRUpTPj7bujlv69i4gIa1V7WvktPTg6MrWR4GgaSQ4EKqWvfwx16DLiBtOEHXL9wsF8MEycpq4aPRFLoho7DG6OZznJBPibjOVhWEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15010","langCode":"en","question":"jPwcD8W74YQFHsaYgF/EjARbitK7VzsdvXQ+ZnUdKEZOStAktQ/6KqKMQPZjrDzWHIsJPHZMfrosKtjujJceBg\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","whose","why","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHXjk7Tc45JWBWq4HhJvrABS2LiAhrVXta+S09ODoytZHtwhg09Zk/0zzUWVTNaaUuVMf2zk9q4A35aDEUZZ5UQUmoZvC6gI2wuVEQ3c5Hnv7XM5HmMCMdEkCH+pxJ6Cj+yx/+HmDBArjDlYSmVI3IccljTiFYHiDXpmCEPfq57SlF+qdwTecocrTsDUjkyG8sY+BhsMqdMkV50G06uUPniYxgjd6FAkhdtKnEPENMBSBQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15011","langCode":"en","question":"RwSfMXx+rGZsQ8H9ah/Z+PXTJ+olHd4OfPwnW+VJi6uDBLb5ecKQLhMaghYK5aQBs/QYiPdKMv00DezH3W67i+nRgpP71YzotcRXCt5jUd+i93hw/O56jmbFNmMx0xxf","answers":["when","whose","why","where"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHV7ltEO5Rh+OFULymFtCWl9sNq2pNEhaPmGlytxXpk1SuQGSpsdRFrF83JuLcP4Jcb1Isg+EjeXyuR3ZIN5tEEszZXD51yxmd5liHaMzBg/heuAXnGGCG1DhvFwHztCSoLFmmGwF1HVLEYgwC01pBxR4+MRWU4lycpHWZi50Zalhw4KOqJftCuvy69PpOeObGSm36TpXERvNEN6wFNAABl/sJktdij864ZaQDsxxz2TfLV/XCXlpkwf6acFuBOIbjZjdAYo0tCRUUm3pLJ9EZS3"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15012","langCode":"en","question":"9FU48k89o9khlBq+o2oLLT9PsO2HJ+L+msH3HG7TnpYbVv9owMlyWXUfchMQVFTOhLa6JuqEUiF/GuMqSSpk2Zej22udadc+0mxx/aRl02jt2Yp224DfVhSpZKmoLPuJWVFedeke0n13r9ytGZtqArVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d","answers":["why","what","how","why not"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14x3r/1UQqeGz1duWJZs+2gk56+Zp5zd9YYyNVWTnV1a8HXyyM8zMQeR4dxZAZSFZRGTBz833gZNu9n+Bv3WXq2DPXUAkV3OQlBgndz3xaUZncDgSAp//pvR83SbTLB4C8CB+FDewBX2EEsoD+3mwVtj5dDD72eTweTG5hFOsn7tsf/h5gwQK4w5WEplSNyHHCHtklg6BDT5pllmDsDQ8NPGmY6qRXDz9Cml2m0kOpzVETQFVMltdCiSP4C7i1ee4dhwRXgX0HpOQSOgE9EWxund7llNoam+XxDaKYmhYQ2nUSz8Opl9A5HmgN9TYMI2+b9Lij1Uft9GSWjvS3XsQNZmmXIDR+wxYPC1nIOHLKyVKiZkGsyxwlAA02C86f113ql1NXjg8u+M/F/iL5daWX4\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15013","langCode":"en","question":"aU5GxETFrFWSUW86R9PWxpva8TX3z1DEr2ZX0Ju4n5sdBdNx2Surgj86iKcKqHcDsCgGB8g5dEHdNgvPpBCdYt6RX9ZAzS3dzgiUESk2QuY\u003d","answers":["why","what","who","when"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17o4T4HXMYM2xHdtA2AAQHXcvcegZAsw06ZPhrbIQ/1Mo8QGsGMX04PmYel+ROeIbximN4viHM0VNVKqufHnRxQCkSVE965ySjF6IccG2nqv0jhdYmUns1/scLDBhhxuSj6OUsSPagku2PxLhKeNMYmugzXVmT+J/yktg70iVSEzW3ztnweHNvjuSNy3QtMBgZHcQOCo6yU/c1f36qzz4ulz7F2i6Rsjjif9DlmsTFk1G7cqraYPvvFAmj9Uk6Ya+H4jRLaC+YFEm2j39W24+iKEWcA2KCmB9GXAOh2Ww3jBCnbXaZU+VRSQHFas5cf8dg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15014","langCode":"en","question":"nMI2ufdf/HJ1LN+Ldwz5iXkrYEb8y5iBLhZTJnH1wbK/SaweHLSyXMJlH3lvD/IpuUI2iijlOlF+YZLGw0XXlg\u003d\u003d","answers":["wherever","why","whoever","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zxdAD+bdmpinupC3BD9Ah/EJJaTVBPkL9OG4GgVAl35Ss1YH09UNPi6snDfz4py4awkmNfC4/8BnRAZxr5MXojv9kTJDP1QDLrYqDTXkYrrw6SJZHNEyLbnhuNuXA04/hu3Kq2mD77xQJo/VJOmGvitnrW5d35qUHmaYbbqj/QSrnolCnUBKTRGmNfQNFkbZ3XwD+aKOpF+Zuxhf99bbTobtyqtpg++8UCaP1STphr4xybFfpz5E5IPdiPEFAJL+MuMGb/MJfJXrRZ2oWYxJRzNVQX6nrBPW5On7YOJL9bOsHZtoreu5grn+Hl/h7a1SaSUGfDGx3d/CgY4Swf8m3ScUPRNSE9loBXwzxWT7I1+ETQFVMltdCiSP4C7i1ee4YLwWwru026X9PXgMS2EpRU\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15015","langCode":"en","question":"YsqiALW5A/6EQfeGfObvoFSOYOcXl1oT3p+F6KABZ5+x2TwZjUBBtz5zY02I4q5Q","answers":["when","why","who","where"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj+Z0iFHjvFipaSAujEOOm90m9MwmscxECoxNYaFQE/Lk3hLGdj9IWZ/Q1C8v/ClJSLkQRXLnzgRq2X3JzksSkQAwM0FEPKFtIEKGkidLRATXrs/8dWk4QJeP1LoMO2Sn/BH2F1ljgs2N77OFBWkD4OTWwqDcfSDcwfGTC4UuVNE38b/BLC6/LAMtlFrBzLwXsi1f1wl5aZMH+mnBbgTiG42WPlkmgdHj2Qk7uhN1o9RBDLew578CEWE5EHhbjx7QrTZWaG4s4PdIUjLaWYMbliOdR/VMrvBX/w11grE+iCjlBu3Kq2mD77xQJo/VJOmGvgkDZh3qCQN2kbhzsKX6xOrtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15016","langCode":"en","question":"06LD5H1DgSeKHZpK487FyaFGNoLTiCBHuvnBqQmKdQRnbs1ynYqTiJwWvMXG09XEXGH9NQz7RqKcxKUF/sNMVsEy2mXpFdqCw4F2PW6sWJM\u003d","answers":["whose","why","where","who"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zTD6uZKNKBQfG1aUkzpTj8n5+lRYUUib5JodcxdRGvx2LiAhrVXta+S09ODoytZHqwCLf3t1Sx/UhBRxy4O4nNB2vM+XaYV+nNRwVi/0p1fZD7TIV3A4AQRU4tLkmuyFvXWcUg5Odw7Otkb/3S8LSCXYhxz3iKrsD3yOKvxcf0UfFy5bTPB1xEzt/PsxLlccRu3Kq2mD77xQJo/VJOmGvgkDZh3qCQN2kbhzsKX6xOrR3kEVyxIeyoeQGU69o/xXNoYaXQVWvCAp6VXLiFMTkTgS4wt3r/VUJdWU+49BJvC"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15017","langCode":"en","question":"U45NyMTY+96bCuwCBkMIGmjQ5qWY0fgPY3vz0Ol4qpNicFaMU/tVXzH5UKRZ9ip03ZGBUL5jmtg6ipCC24boY96DmhitIlcj+W4SL/h2V08\u003d","answers":["how long","how much","how often","how many"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16aO8LXlNyToEkwj3Wov9Zl0edHElP8NDHToCflyW4GYFeuUz9P2fRjlwwgXgPLYd2K8aVcG/1wJH54VSXrvK8OALwMtGH9l/ADb/ltR0zYnQ+bqW9/kQWZSYxk1DuIW4a3IxOLRbLibroeMFkNTSPZRVXOTGvJvog46KfrtTtP/A0bFKjjHrZZwn7qm7UHwkAduSVZKd/Krry7fqKouvnjrzQSGcbMc0zWeZnjVFNz4rFO03fu6aj8Tv/ooMz9rwkXRLLWNVBl3GUFD8K8hDNUE9wutvv1OUEA38q1kJJULI7tVLbkhpRSdp5H1xFExumHrfiWadk2a9+6yTbFRj/sDeKKlmGR++L7HliQf8ws5buHBxxTgm/KbVMJk8GeOTCBQwcUexU2QHLDFf77Y2Dv4tUSZF79qWv6P1OALFspmVeMVOV+Hf5BnKsE2MS0wVwGQK6CnRkFze1n0McPEzGc\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15018","langCode":"en","question":"aRVkOZADsdLC+IASCWSwSo9odSHXG9CBc7LmPOTWE34mlCqtsw0HV4g+zXPCmQinUMgngxOy4Mt1F+RMnx6r0ULTa7ap6fkT8nSUrL+N3t4\u003d","answers":["how many","how long","how much","how often"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1xBMu/B+S1vT1RMY3UrWsBalnrbqFVV+llGRLziqPO8wKbO7oU5ed5MlX906CTXhnijQHe0WB5DOgc0yFVBkbRA/wDhY0TMbZAYQopt5bTEodwvcSOQSO4xv5B+p4BNA0nLgJu0XIVNjgnm05JPH1KHnqIkc2OP5+O3rUjn6threQWpmUUTrC271yQP/3ujfGw4HH4M9+iaVjOHY0C+EF7lzQfC9eVuHwhbvymv58e7klV1KVKAZLMqR0RZGubFwt6ylMD7Js9ERFC3cCVsO4JpF6+5GBqpD9rXtt4I0rz8whOBLtoZ4nIutR368PZFL4wINNTtupFAGNwF+nTenOrH9iMl6EPEtkqG2O+bYIRNhtGntDDs/IQshWCsVzVtUjrVwmAY2j2r7s5LaJz9cbHTX3sq0GubZ0yBq7EB3MXTN4VpZe0XVXKa5ffrDrBPZyPli4wc780Zb5FkgE6dfBRm1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15019","langCode":"en","question":"+yiglndRdI7+bzoZEJe0Ia3kca/8rUiLOtQOuVzi4fTM/Dpy91kwXsM5xn0uzbp4JIue0WmmiamRK5SGsLbjy3akK3axCe2nelvnojWLs1A\u003d","answers":["how much","how long","how far","how many"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x10By8w1pQ23CR/jdQPuVQYdAFnVNyoE8ZEbWCBm0FMUiDGj+Hjou11ZQBqAUnDtZ4FBFJxwmgKHI8gQhx5w1l+zyxdocAh2lZ4lYH5nV2mhG7n2JXblbgpNGbRVFjLaJkESf52518am12ojga5aqbrQo0B3tFgeQzoHNMhVQZG0QP8A4WNEzG2QGEKKbeW0xKIKIBPkzMc+IALG8hL70nvcjAqnzil0A+35d+DQW57O2TULj+TWzfcGkVF8snwxErUVvMhJOAjg5VQkMhKurTJPYcEV4F9B6TkEjoBPRFsbpuoylNjBTiJAvr0GzvlFdXXTNVZPFCKMtq8HlIUbMlBursWFBWh5PBTLHxRmzTU2CXJEAeIjTZdpikQKqxp48CWFw40P9KRYByO0iAckhsbk5pta0H0cSY3VqbED0DK9AV7b+mB7Ex7EyYG1WOeqFRoX4GoPEBUX9NemvNNuE6Og\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15020","langCode":"en","question":"Q6Lh5oVMXuNZBZ+tlLIDW5onGW1XNIyfMiWzhcPPs5pQJ8NJPzPnEK0YelEH1SGL+zjmxfCiXsAHe2xIJ3+St+wWnhCI97kNvFw5rgBsdPc\u003d","answers":["who","where","how","whose"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12H+GhTPOR6N4U1dG4Qrqfu9W2Tga64uqm78u4asX+3/xZphsBdR1SxGIMAtNaQcUVNjkDodU1kSTKSqYoZUtVLdiwTW0V6r8nmd7YEHhAC5oiuH8eY02ySOxGMTadr7Y/QcEQnCfqlDsX1gNf3VIdlSi2UgXmc9fmFhmNNhbZ8BCsfi9ApQ7G+yMuxksDq3n1g45Mi2R9HxHj634ctjavihvDn+a3GcVtfD5wN1zrm6q+u0qvq5e7zZuNmC1F6af6J51nIPtW+2x3AyvjqXBkiOxIm/ydmBmKbcMhh1K3z9PyaNn176Cms3Y2vV7vM8Kp2YIBjkl9HT7sq9j2As2VJsxAmMst//nwI9OgcxH4VGWIcPJzNUJSkU9m3rSiadfDvAxzPaPMO8ILZFI0NZE9BZeu1S0Btr7DrljIHt6w3q"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15021","langCode":"en","question":"QPP+NIZLI1EqAbQtec7bGtV7twtM4Ec6qUzHL/wnKUKfhWL9xC1SRT2Fec6yHP0yhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["whose","how","who","where"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12H+GhTPOR6N4U1dG4Qrqfu9W2Tga64uqm78u4asX+3/xZphsBdR1SxGIMAtNaQcUVNjkDodU1kSTKSqYoZUtVLdiwTW0V6r8nmd7YEHhAC5oiuH8eY02ySOxGMTadr7Y/QcEQnCfqlDsX1gNf3VIdlSi2UgXmc9fmFhmNNhbZ8BCsfi9ApQ7G+yMuxksDq3n1g45Mi2R9HxHj634ctjavihvDn+a3GcVtfD5wN1zrm6q+u0qvq5e7zZuNmC1F6af6J51nIPtW+2x3AyvjqXBkiOxIm/ydmBmKbcMhh1K3z9PyaNn176Cms3Y2vV7vM8Kp2YIBjkl9HT7sq9j2As2VJsxAmMst//nwI9OgcxH4VGWIcPJzNUJSkU9m3rSiadfDvAxzPaPMO8ILZFI0NZE9BZeu1S0Btr7DrljIHt6w3q"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15022","langCode":"en","question":"0e+ZezJqCXixzilJhXd6Bz69rIrTMFmFCNSyyaeAf/yszy9y41UtSPQUwZOKzM9qd3pqc5+HzL7LPEBhafjecQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["how often","how about","how long","how many"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x10lh/VRmf2aYPpf1vrdGxRjtRgh98opxSuLMH0sVtxvdWOFVjoypWlf04ijrsnTno39ubl3mGn3mPJGeg4kwJ/VKPnPyXIRzLdoKFx19+bp5vcUHtTbu9zJZ9vRGdeYXZ04FgXZgTY0xJFBxaTqWbNNv236nBxShp0iBrBL9zm83Ttb1S8tAaETJPtV6btmUMKxWIEMc8mVkJ1/9fovKyiwhQebmKODzR5kmpgiF1Lu8y5OTjKlD0Vsn8mbMqFSYXF0BXaX/4WJwgDSIwrUT8lTTNSFUHC5wluJDPiY9BoGc6Afb51ZiAxrw/468gwGF21GylblfXhWLAz0i9t0eaQp7Jf18gDcpzpCYrjUAf7+yfTtC1rVw1CuaA2/t1A5CTYR8X7BJY6jqup4nZgmSzHBTFT4CRt7q6yUw3CjqOd8T1h978YJx/tBt1gcpYzHKPTkiPaKlyk70mRvA5QWQxQMabHVEU2aEk8KYC5nbyrf4hG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15023","langCode":"en","question":"VdG+lcRrGYYIU+RhQqajZwPxroptgDYVcUM53AkPGMizUSRVrBZ0z4S4oq7DPhuBlUlWmWB5RHI89o4rCiAh5g\u003d\u003d","answers":["how many","how often","how much","how long"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wBJhLwdSusAk7uYugqzIb9/HFitYTBNRkEEnvwxH/Ev8jBvQwNIn/ATSG8kznjzASjQHe0WB5DOgc0yFVBkbRA/wDhY0TMbZAYQopt5bTEogogE+TMxz4gAsbyEvvSe9yMCqfOKXQD7fl34NBbns7ZNQuP5NbN9waRUXyyfDEStvFEqq3Z0w2jENjJcL1QC0xAYUD5Cvz576AgIhe58CJfKrd0sRc1TjF2MY34/8IClut7ODX5mHQP0dP8KeWHyci4SrFOkCQ1lWPprmr9P0M68lZ3hWabCR4jT0b2pcJOBfZMFuSQ7hd+LHk5rHT75uKAdG3ZIBGh33X24m62sTOKuJYsyY4oEmnZyznMAWzpTuuG2GB43Qcx9jPPe3PK6ReITyqn4FxQ5uXU7u3qwPB1DiZ/AMB3pe3TKSUXLSsKyHdzMebEZzoygoVdTJ4/s2nucRbbddTc7BMGK4vn3/hyLkSviNtdR4gq+Fs9KowUReqhgfNurjopEfDZDSyeV8SjlePRDFGuWO+F3jUFrZqQ\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15024","langCode":"en","question":"1KU5S7vix/3iK5Ay28FdC4e+Z4QR6i1ev6Yw1q/1G7fS2M3xRW5kufOGjnwV5bifw9+Y7uD62PS1IedpBpL1vORmBf2Fh5EtfGWSTUnG3tB3empzn4fMvss8QGFp+N5x","answers":["why","when","whose","which"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AmJIRWd1lNMLJ6Z/z/FZh5B4WdGTZrHIWs5c5KalxVbmePTJKCAXw/HMXV2/cak8TTlNqsn3uI/nm+DHZvaYk4RBd5nSTjVhMMyuy1Pjv7mmyTZ1QmYqZLiSO6xDl6eY+Ta/n+F01/vXYB5Si985mS6lUwSizuOl3s2cjAbppPlydMn6gtZUdtdubIzZsuItFOvxRRYoUEMhLqgYv7dNA9ViBkLW50dWcV+9jF/QCUrq2zUKGAp//52rroeuNWv5VL11nFIOTncOzrZG/90vC0gl2Icc94iq7A98jir8XH9FEeICWswNRrAKSPl1EsW3TXSOF1iZSezX+xwsMGGHG5KJUP+e2FjXeIAxDWAB4hpew\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15025","langCode":"en","question":"IloorXmIHO72GOS3c1RzUW9F3nl8+TcEX8efr1kdhXoF78QocdnGme8fHnJTUIS0jExgeeG/TYIw/KVbdYJw9g\u003d\u003d","answers":["why","who","which","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AnzBzr1+m99IzWES9UZX31rM3V7bPeoweB91ox8hfoZTScR1utyYRiArEaqGbfmv/32tmRtLyZs7jfzXNDpaNT3rK3vUI2m8YX154oqLPfrfbkrn5H4dXhT8vMHkqn/Fo9XUeUKbskOEsVK3GQSxRvitX9cJeWmTB/ppwW4E4huNkKUqY+3NUkEOSE2Z/m5DEHRTv3tgxq/gOjsmJI7Qa3qpt+k6VxEbzRDesBTQAAZfxDs9AuiIa5tu96CJeRl3eoRNAVUyW10KJI/gLuLV57hgBrrG+tplV12UJqzcU1TyfJxe3cPIn9Sf436aaVr5ICEbzIZIy8f/vBQNmIt/pHh"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15026","langCode":"en","question":"zP3Hz8UXndLYhknPGmkBm1s6SNcPhHHM3T6P2RNkNiFmRpiassr6lYTTJAk8aar2HY5HYjcSzBr/3LWl/Lwv7XWw05//V77BTPL9g1k8ifodUvLvz2iINKvprVUu6/dBe0O2m2WWIFer1Z0HlHHPHQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["how","whose","which","when"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AnzBzr1+m99IzWES9UZX31rM3V7bPeoweB91ox8hfoZTScR1utyYRiArEaqGbfmv/3k6eyHVqkSz32w98gRWyWdExrpB+xTWjwTauItUCUdRVt87Z8Hhzb47kjct0LTAYGR3EDgqOslP3NX9+qs8+Lptkn6I+Dn6eJX3hrLYfcsYavrtKr6uXu82bjZgtRemn9hXMHxUT1Cau1WQ05FOl/AMIY1HX81t5fF5U5RWafRItKmyzh60a3hLmPcgYla8MVQPq3maF1ht209DfVacZN6r6uaqnAKIRSHcJj8OYiIkzHaXrxH5C6kFnyy1QCbrv4\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15027","langCode":"en","question":"/2Pgm0g9tGBdraPuL57BLHu2xjkQNMK3PFWdyeW5gzqeZhk1buGhOHK0kN5p9BXxrERg/wJKZ1jVrvFRFlD5qA\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","what","who","whose"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX+khZ7deemytfM7xR6WBgye1DFs3swAEjjw20tiSklvdoSx9xuYIhAGJBaTUoVUIaHvIgN7AeJQEfq2EH1xvWjRrzIyyCB501uPoTTj+ZXMFYOmYuhSjFU4Fb0u3Setgva+sjhEPOqwDn2o/cY5sLjA0U797YMav4Do7JiSO0Gt6qbfpOlcRG80Q3rAU0AAGX8Q7PQLoiGubbvegiXkZd3qETQFVMltdCiSP4C7i1ee4YAa6xvraZVddlCas3FNU8nycXt3DyJ/Un+N+mmla+SAhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15028","langCode":"en","question":"+V9EKLZvc+aINjBQlzQ8g2dowrde2jhVFsYpk+OCVwJ+DrumjmS+ylrFCanhPJQXMsb/qziZst9w5Ii2yKmFcA\u003d\u003d","answers":["which","why","how","whose"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14tysGYiYZHCt/iKhLiZZX+khZ7deemytfM7xR6WBgye1DFs3swAEjjw20tiSklvdt+X42P3oV3cOzIIYfSyBlP4RfnMA2tDekmpLs4xhFRRkGYfU3jP0j4lZ+CNXAlNVNi4gIa1V7WvktPTg6MrWR6/bifViO7XsdTQtPnpIXvD5fzD+cyFfCn9ZZ/NmFhcok0zFhiqowS0Mb9ClkSafJPp7hRb8uW7Ei8FsGjWXeGteRdqZ6/RjhOmD/pgHtrNci4fPLalxFyXDZmXmEI9oOHARVGqihkAcrL1EUgVTFmhtVUODdij2ujqueBKZTpfGQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15029","langCode":"en","question":"j8kS7gc0nh1SNp4G+6CEkdbrGtrQuT4+lT37IwcKHBTjZktRtmfulpXC+aV7ZoNyQbp9GVC05Ra7vPsa1+fqYg\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","what","which","why"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x17wUJ7GYJ1O0hxv6qd0UvJCNMVHYDYREMgedkM4Gk0qBuZEDb3/ZWLPR9hrofUbFKHZQplcxf2+Zj09NpGJYYd2+21qwHGK68cXP6Gt6tXOI+ESfl6AmFROgweqdpK48HZwg0MyhjIHYSkcEwx0RcVopH2xF6ElWqyUqitHEc75dq+u0qvq5e7zZuNmC1F6af/Ff0BMxuSNW/YMTF5/LwjHiJ3WQu+se72Hyjphi34rj4GBrVweWnEWQWSN+kjFezMArKk+O1jxf25hesFxc3fs+BhsMqdMkV50G06uUPniYxgjd6FAkhdtKnEPENMBSBQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15030","langCode":"en","question":"LVLmWAcwaVlVJ/IXnEw5J7gFEsLGcO/4HVAeXjSojpFqS08Wuph42EwdW0ClHSliuGAggpSQvMidWEbPpd76XkQBSZZd7N3YZ2/K/pi04la1VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z","answers":["was","is","has","had"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19/6UAee5sDg6DmWGHd17fcclvHy2QRmj/cF3WS9tYaOnI7yerl/L8gRyNaJA8TwbEqcVgkKzdMpAqNQilIz90ReTK1L1AVBnvursMaSNst/Dv4ShqdWhfAPeqTeJIZbzWlFrhCZo+YlSLUZJTRJ0dsWF9R/5Ashhat0Xcwecvdi4vFXehV+ZAz5gM3HT26gd8Wv4YclKPkNpOC+mVgrDjf5/tXjtSwbNXuCZRZrqM+efWYZBxv8JtT9nFVSJTGuVird5Vo0xfoJ4YUHwy1NQ+2/ZXZcyzVL1Cj2EsG+GQwsgx/3675QGVH9vakgnUvMSQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15031","langCode":"en","question":"CSnTFE/uIhmYzskUXsXeU6MaVioTKf6SnTSdq+rYDdE3XqFOqQp6q9lytdNzR+nfnVMVqv3VRSYcaYurIkrgFFwiRD1M5gR2tFJLui4R5Nkez1tiA1DOySLaUQ6pszPg","answers":["do","does","are","is"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x12RjBOG0bw1TEwg2kI+Yg5YY5XjNKCo34bRJPXDsrjy5H3la6CctjhwG8CyWFxuTLbsMHgv1JmhZJPCtpT6RTNtIH2PFkQWA2GcYiUEwijWB3xQdV0bsRdeKisclz0aqAo/c575oZFUndNnmirmUWP5FGz5JknYlD8ZfRQtpEBYcJqsqxdkNbELcT0tqoHx1rGI6yXA00a2F83MYUQpMS9ZRu+hEsgd66GMUh6qsMBuMRS4yyfTAO9moixcFPCt/qSY+su0Vxxw5FMCZAE34d/TSHszi0niamZk/OP46pxg/rCOcJZNMeQBgAZ7L/s4N7g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15032","langCode":"en","question":"uhzD7SDpm2kUb6eor4O2v50EYO5uCmgEgbwnVVHgDeFdeP234Bj8nlbKDgb2H7j2YHdlvcL6MbDgHD9CJ2JbY2SiUcPjeoJ9cI6fBKpjQiurD+UUUcpKPCdplk9n7lalri1+BGPvJvVYlD/IwMe2Nw\u003d\u003d","answers":["is","were","are","was"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1803uwk0jG7wCdS6vAO1LzBu1qGC1wRnbd45lgxW289TljNe95i2yKGZjJu8ITyrFiASIS2/Sgmx5DRlmJoq9F/Hi2Xu4pzM6YIJv0iUIF70B42CA8+cqVaPg9oUNl2xVBOH6nmJToWMCfwbbV0eLhH4IdwQq+s7pD1LthzpTpr1OL92iEB2qDE1xBMluT7UwU2hujszToi1aH0T8cew2fuhE34XGQJmyqXTiUoYBjsQ1r7AXRYP5M4L7Zfq/17y1bEnN0O39jqlArl4uEzRO7sHDVn86lNsZglsSVYPxqEFwh87u3fUXxhngRqx40Mw1YRvMhkjLx/+8FA2Yi3+keE\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15033","langCode":"en","question":"RW9/kXWN3BU81V8IG7O+HLd9VMAcdN0DaNu9x7mYiayxnNlO+MkwbbCwvKU7rnalrzOqq/Lh51jKk5xQs6TCEMFzES2mIKuQDWragE5m6rDNSmgNIwEMdoCssF/IaDSSGhk2XLj8B+ChS//UG5dj5A\u003d\u003d","answers":["do","does","didn’t","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16+Au/kxIeGRpA5n0iLjuM1u1qGC1wRnbd45lgxW289TljNe95i2yKGZjJu8ITyrFiASIS2/Sgmx5DRlmJoq9F/Hi2Xu4pzM6YIJv0iUIF70B42CA8+cqVaPg9oUNl2xVBOH6nmJToWMCfwbbV0eLhH4IdwQq+s7pD1LthzpTpr1OL92iEB2qDE1xBMluT7UwU2hujszToi1aH0T8cew2fuhE34XGQJmyqXTiUoYBjsQ1r7AXRYP5M4L7Zfq/17y1bEnN0O39jqlArl4uEzRO7sHDVn86lNsZglsSVYPxqEFwh87u3fUXxhngRqx40Mw1bVVDg3Yo9ro6rngSmU6Xxk\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15034","langCode":"en","question":"gZ9ymRFwawYouekVi3cRhd/Y+vUSScQYN5foqUnvBiy5AajtpTIwNh6/012fdUdWQ4HfPWEF+FeYEuRcmlSdpQmA2rYbk7Ue/MxU9fNznVF4CZavU/iDE9xNrfxH+HV/Ju+qRDy4cFR5cUzeS/0vAw\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","will","shouldn’t","won’t"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zaWElA3vxzcbryUSkU2DvfTn2/8UPRJu/ZD4FZMwWKAGFdwuAetKQzkDpPOmQk+hNYIlJItNOKfUKkxRti/9qmbXkJMzhPJZfSCE+TwPmG3M5jf5Fe9ZKnF09rMg+LqsvZ7K/xDayhoGLJJhV/IJQ/LTZ8/xTkHecx7fKomAMAmPO4uM7RZjZtLkvqF9z4DgDIPWF14qOS7xsyBC38QYfGtaz1gQ/fBvLlFtL/L4YZhviPWApLSaCCuCt4/V3bwzEWL5MqFBB20qBFvaszAUxI\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15035","langCode":"en","question":"PSx4Yit0w4/jzbCEW5n+Q7uB3ImOKeIK3KvXWASRZNCWV4tF8HG3OEtFccdSjmkwdr57q6QBCGZb56oX7LU4wg\u003d\u003d","answers":["doesn’t","don’t","didn’t","do"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1wYo5HJ/w0Nhm7joZUZoPM8Fh4M5VAmW1lJtWrrB5G6JjMGC8Qo7EJEe4kS8XEAYsdGY6XiE/UXoONYEJEi/ChG0prMKh5PjOLhuJhCfQfSJyK5n746t/4OZ18YNTn3sfQpW1UePHNyqNsMAO7+XqCAFaWLHh0FQA2GEUD6GmbDBvw8puUzvvANsV8xMq0lXyfyMJw330mj/2B6Q+Y82wWEvb5EXQAKCBzZigUbOjyAN"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15036","langCode":"en","question":"40UnjTB+MPwFUAHUTxKR7TBNufZGu2NvSKNM8+6pqkLPH0Tm3bPUveR2YG8tdG6oOCblGuv4VHaqy4gxIsJVzQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["when","why","who","what"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13irs9WqkPZFc366RrT9j0idyHFm8I5NgxtN+ZYVsiF5D5xMA/UgtZfszyphvBB9ZI/wneTGbQiL8AwASB3GPucjo6ZhgTEpRIlSxY90Dcr17ZnJ9Z63xyLLKDCIas0T0BFQ4u0m6Erxxiv2NjWaa0mIGQtbnR1ZxX72MX9AJSurieAroadRxqxPWct+r/6RK6vrtKr6uXu82bjZgtRemn+9t4whEgE14b/qccXrL2/VgeHUk1e/bXxuTSt0GHtwpVXo3KHDlY+vL82S1v5drLZGFl2IP/2/Ucpu7DCG3brYRS/Pj1Wj34xyngQB3guP6g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15037","langCode":"en","question":"r5+Qxw8Uw/QMoBgHHA1csezi6N1lnvC0hWk6f2dR8wHKvRAsSHyIkcYJi63ONdgc","answers":["why","what","when","which"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x13irs9WqkPZFc366RrT9j0hDOV8NVe+KuxDu91MfUQW+trIFxSgOac8NO4txfFhvxLREo/aF+ZXYURf/OrNzb9U8nwT0kY6YaYjkjxvK51jRoWShdFiop6DvLHElaVZYou3eB7YGKOcRQAL/wpOLX25KMLgv/Jvc33ESW5n+dwt3Y4Rui8JEHvBDI1n0CRWUxaN3evlWBu54KLA+G6VrEjdPP0Omph16H9dakWZNCRaLY4ao3RJlwiUusa36np6pyBFQ4u0m6Erxxiv2NjWaa0mIGQtbnR1ZxX72MX9AJSurieAroadRxqxPWct+r/6RK6vrtKr6uXu82bjZgtRemn+9t4whEgE14b/qccXrL2/VNGZ//wn1v3zFG25sDYuybWNHhZMBSnWPXpHhCcg8YDGV/I4jvpQGmJ2IhzI3vpey"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15038","langCode":"en","question":"2Bh9tRWsHvMjEs8hg+t2tAWVqVIxT14vSWVVT6ZwWCTykGzKMyAnNdx4dsS8hjzwCIEnoKJuzxFOI81KmQOENnzCF8naWSFCLTt/wt43VbKbzEeQPwip6WQstf1YWHL7","answers":["couldn’t","could","should","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x111wxDexBQK7HaFh5Jfxa3QAOhq2KQNGT887y+WloNuDkH+Vj1haYNxAjFVn3oZjSHmvRIbnDkCSP7rOFXt5H1AU/swV666GibLkf0gJpDfM5sulWPLWP7LAeXRYp7NCged4tjDxCI2Ba5XoAxVtmoBpoqBfJmt2yfmdVhtlaLQJTQzeruflwFhzXFrxAem88NxHo+vJtbDh1uDk54qRROY\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15039","langCode":"en","question":"24QCfsLvGGqpIJFOvrCTupBlv3hdLn930E+W9rHc7D61Ry8LaSrQgExF8OHwdtZvdOw/HBJ4/j3aZoUDMbozppwHtumcI4Qw2tsMeTk73k8\u003d","answers":["were","are","aren’t","was"],"correctAnswer":2,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19MlXnE9vLhLOf+kH8WObZ+Ng8pndhf4mLbwIUuInJuTjaFHizefkny5/vftsuwxJmlj+AvNPwQ2dpuxbuzZrQ5nM95DAFEtDKS110giFf0cXMVO0xFz6JdOjGz17FSZhkYWEzjiCfNGlUht4fOtygn/0r6YVEJmiL3WWE+4TlxbLhUYqalsZItNdIJP0Men6ad427WKSQEVsHA78dQdv4eFzPuVU3NhKJ+AN6lLWA+XYV4iaUwBN26j/z2rArbzLTt5ekB/O8pVxqp9H3QfEPSQT5RwMN+Ww7zmN6dc7eZIDPAoEAPyF/fcpyG0qqrr81nYxNyhvbuK7/wpe19Sqv46ncd+uy6UNRANyjmquHZ6"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15040","langCode":"en","question":"KdJsLGm3h1TppgWNNLat/f5Evim0q/pnFA7nMJK6r4nw75ytUDhxlXNygyYSVz9zaQrxKkQ7Sw5bN5phJpGWxQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["does","do","don’t","did"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x16+Au/kxIeGRpA5n0iLjuM0dVeUjguUVojUgt0vUNi88foXaQgaoby1rTeSQRpz7Cv1+LA5DIJS8GoGrbwK8xlEAMdxxpE3FOfqq4luto+0X+m8lxcrpdgUDPjBvn5x9VSXkpQBl8m2LBFkrZKTtqR/l6vkYBgjuYGJClF/SasuEk+4zhFZ44ti+DYzhv7sr8g\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15041","langCode":"en","question":"6lUA2BZbwr79549Pc8Rvs86QMGE40Vlvp1mqsV40g/25p4CVuf5G/Hrb0k0fOC0N+CJJadqqH56WSS+ygboWaXd6anOfh8y+yzxAYWn43nE\u003d","answers":["why","when","how","which"],"correctAnswer":3,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14rnKqztzRrbOuE1I8sk+AkLatedUWjZ14L2i070cATELykUuGXETvQknkuI5dAVPNzNO6h5JnJjVq6UwlwKFofC7L8ZLSsv+zQvuc2lv+2SF/Qmz+sjhBdTDS2UQbRmMfXWcUg5Odw7Otkb/3S8LSA3cZONOjT9/K58yCMKIS+kwUynUg1vbw8Z1cQtx6/FeQ6pO2AM+ROUqXJ70lFowo9qBntb6Phr29w7IpNZG4hp2LiAhrVXta+S09ODoytZHm36nJe5elAJe8InzTUeyE9HU8gtBMdA52FNYHtXnaeBJXo7/KqKCKN3YThj8iITzQ\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15042","langCode":"en","question":"oE8ywS84AjgjdEEbrQAHBTxCbvVoAy1pob2+RaZp5+ZxIGdOWRl7HQo20AIs57OE0majr6X5hymgEEiy2ny7I8EPYFWwUytPUZ2VWtCTPVXamEFhq0A5S8PVu2CMjEBn","answers":["is","are","was","were"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x18IinH0ZKINa7V4sGZSLviZu1qGC1wRnbd45lgxW289TljNe95i2yKGZjJu8ITyrFq1NTXzAP2QKirJ3JFdrwkZJc/MNuQ0oIj4m2x4JXdkp"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15043","langCode":"en","question":"gAK9B0LHsF4mG4C8WR7qmMtZIfaCVUyYjhR2MzBZLJgHbtDumAP5b1fp5fYJ+c2N3HnbzRKRKHvoGVgWT4yk4G6QiWBf8jtL1OF5BlqcTLYZmvULq13QMzlVAET7xaPW","answers":["where","which","why","when"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":1,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1w28Zbwcl93z9kzwuOJmV/rzkxIkinKRSLe6RTdltDUL2LiAhrVXta+S09ODoytZHva6INuimaqUlmvDN8lTK65HeQRXLEh7Kh5AZTr2j/Fc2hhpdBVa8ICnpVcuIUxORJ+Yxoh7EBMYh6MVB4eMXDbYuICGtVe1r5LT04OjK1keBoGkkOBCqlr38Mdegy4gbThB1y/cLBfDBMnKauGj0RS6IaOwxujmc5yQT4m4zlYVhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15044","langCode":"en","question":"NfVv3pIDIGsAM/sWt2dpabrKvMshHgGLmkEundrT95vx22blOYHH3FVI/m8uRDzlYKg4dbLDlMR/9wgLoiGd8w\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","can","must","do"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19eziQOV6l/Iw5Kn5QuRQX+io6a5WXnYsq61d80TYIvhRIt5uqw/cQK81MbBfD/oYebNKMQVFUXGvcazFzqm3IqASpEraLNVTxdGwCwHYSoLgVWr2x4H9IflphKaDohRvPtVTAfpkjBXU61lDVOwm+K6Vuu5WagdekVtzFR3mykzEUDruSCIRN2izWlsPqvf4Q\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15045","langCode":"en","question":"JmhdTEcdcsTLAiLFI2O9aLaBDgnvI0keN0454NWLu9+Nah7Zy5VA2tGhjn5BoDshXo0kHDu8WhK86J0mCHvyeFOQkBFxYGMRXW2TDfXQ1261VQ4N2KPa6Oq54EplOl8Z","answers":["couldn’t","could","should","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1592Vm1XAodAwwcwhr9jqIH0XWU58lZtLA3tDqBwcDsXDOAb/gg8vB0QPgrzVaP6bA18LbmRXKKnqWMvFP2JqOokMSd3KmtfxP6FHrHtei6ZuLPucqB8+TZXBgnvIIqTxw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15046","langCode":"en","question":"3p1g2Rdxwumj5fmUk/DICw14zQELcQSR4nnkSljXG1kUF7KSvTEb1jJqoCT6qtbsVvlGJWITLHXuqygTOfxymJ26EyLrGrCJWXxUcSGeqhk\u003d","answers":["would","wouldn’t","should","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14+5+5e2uKrP985DRHVjinlo5m6UJtvu3f0SZLuRLYpIrwy5lwGwdTn9/roEAa7FUd2+3gxa4JEMU6KpH6z93z/88/H2Qgw99sK9Ea4RY5nsgtGkUue0OxjmUi5v8yHGLg\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15047","langCode":"en","question":"vXYLmplAoSjlOuPEZhlCyIpQo7TbfYbRJCTLzar4Ibwd8mu3imdEDAthN/tIp1VuhG8yGSMvH/7wUDZiLf6R4Q\u003d\u003d","answers":["would","wouldn’t","should","shouldn’t"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x14+5+5e2uKrP985DRHVjinn0XWU58lZtLA3tDqBwcDsXZ+/8K798lPbH2qE5DmEXMKF3WbhrRgTEpXtWzvfnzDWsplOLWy3qV1qttLIW60oKV+gmP59odjyVFP+2tOlHreMepodorFUEhX4M7hpw3W4\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15048","langCode":"en","question":"AOnaVT0nWGjIUSS/E7dcfAHd0V/+zePKIJKcshdiWf+2JnsfZPtDlE+BRYBElVW9","answers":["must","can","shall","should"],"correctAnswer":1,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x19eziQOV6l/Iw5Kn5QuRQX9JsrHUO0nkRlt9ZgDqmud5czXBnAnmi3MABwdIedzEKZ3IYe1FMhUjd4cA72c1fJp5Ez8jssU2pX73x3fPhKCE30BQCsyNYIFdnr8ZAktduw\u003d\u003d"},{"topicId":"15","id":"15049","langCode":"en","question":"JmhdTEcdcsTLAiLFI2O9aE51pZ1GgrKLs3jmsioryCt1MEkCFqOy5U058tjsr+TlCfp05rECcIronYPbL7Rg22QkhVLAPkL/H5p5LyxlxTIrchrAMs8NRgQSrgliUeachYTjK+CS3KpIawTCdSwz9uZKJ+pzQVxOkoh/l23vNqPb3VgBV2BxyN5FCqtoKynrPmCEDKIuvBI+9HNk27AMUQ\u003d\u003d","answers":["should","could","will","must"],"correctAnswer":0,"level":2,"explanation":"enXGGbAlfAHYW7KhBX5x1zaWElA3vxzcbryUSkU2DvcRbsNa6ElxE9a2gOrxABa6OU0hPnQ0sRFkv6zHuj6WUEGFR54HUotPoeQLXpAF237XSlPVi3H7WM/LdtWVVtxGnnMDkc2EQnEk09oufF69JA\u003d\u003d"}]